Christopher Chandra

Address: Woolloongabba, QLD 4102

Mobile: 0432 644 477

Personal Website: christopherchandra.info Email: christopher_chandra@outlook.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-chandra-9601bb1b9/

Profile

Master's graduate Computer Science with skills in Web and Mobile Application Development, Object Oriented Programming, and scrum IT Project Management. QUT graduate with experience across various projects utilizing Agile methodology of Project Management. Strong knowledge in React, JavaScript and C# and a passion to work collaboratively with a team. Ability to consistently finish tasks with a high level of efficiency and keen to commence a career in Information Technology.

Education

Laucation	
ACS Professional Year Program in Computer Science/ICT Navitas Professional, Brisbane	Mar 2022 - Ongoing
Master of Information Technology - Computer Science Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane	Aug 2021 - Jul 2022
Bachelor of Information Technology - Computer Science Queensland University of Technology, Brisbane	Jan 2020 - Aug 2021

Employment History

Tobacco SG, Everton Park, QLD

Sales Attendant Sep 2022 - Ongoing

- Demonstrate efficiency in financial transaction using POS with 0% error
- Exceed customer satisfaction with effective communication

Mitra Agung, Maumere, Indonesia

IT Freelancer Jan 2017 – Ongoing

- Establish effective data design and structure utilising Excel
- Manage the database using google drive for cost effective data storage
- Prototype solutions using third-party software

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477

Email: christopher_chandra@outlook.com

Degree Related Projects

QUT, Blockchain-Based Assessment Ledger Website

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a website that exceed our client's requirements within a span of 6 months.
- Demonstrated skills in JavaScript front-end development
- Achieved success in testing SDN using Linux virtual OS
- Used Trello for quality control

QUT Foundry, Gamified Entrepreneur Dashboard

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Queensland University of Technology

- Successfully created a website that satisfied the client's requirements within a duration of 1 year
- Designed front end of the website with HTML and CSS
- Implemented back end of the website with Phyton
- Organized workflow using SCRUM method
- Documented the coding of the project
- Fixed bugs and troubleshoot the website

UBAYA University, Final Exams Scheduling Website

Jan 2018 - Jan 2019

University of Surabaya, Christopher

- Successfully created a website that met the client's satisfaction within a timeframe of 1
 year
- Implemented PHP for backend development
- Designed the front-end using HTML

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477

Email: christopher_chandra@outlook.com

Key Skills

Coding Skills	Skills
• C#	Technical Skills:
• .NET	 Experience with scrum project management method
PHP	 Codes with a focus in object-oriented programming
HTML	 Ability to develop an Entity Relationship Diagram
• CSS	Soft Skills:
JavaScript	Strong team working skills demonstrated via lack of negative
React.js	outcomes when working collaboratively with a team
React-	 Adaptability shown by working as front and back-end roles.
native	 Integrity shown by maintaining complete honesty with both my
Python	team and manager.
SQL	

Memberships

• Australian Computer Society (ACS) membership Member

Referees

Referees are available upon request

Christopher Chandra Phone: 0432 644 477

Email: christopher_chandra@outlook.com